# **CHANRITH "HONG" LEATHENG**

8642793641 https://hong-webport.github.io/ lhcr.workline@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/hong-leatheng-4aaa5b200/ https://github.com/Hong-webport

## **TECH PROFESSIONAL**

Multi-skilled IT Professional, committed to lifelong learning with a love and respect to solving problems, team collaborations and collective improvements. Skilled in Bash, Data Analysis and Visualization using Python and JavaScript, along with Tableau, Guardium and Splunk. Continue with, more machine learning Al and statistics. Have experience in CyberSecurity, Data Analysis and Automation.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python | JavaScript | SQL | HTML | CSS | Splunk | Bash | Pandas | Flasks | D3 | Leaflet | Matplotlib | SKlearns | ETL | API Calls | RESTAPI | Web Scraping | Machine Learning | Written Robot Programs for Industrial Robots such as KUKA, ABB, Staubli. | Written PLC Programs: Siemens | DirectLogix | Microsoft Azure | IBM Security Guardium | MS Visual Code | IBM Security Guardium Big Data Intelligence (GBDI) | Splunk | Tableau | Adobe Creative Suite | Siemen TIA 3 | NI Multisims | Anaconda Jupyter Lab | Postgres SQL | Google Collab | Cloud Infrastructure | Android Studio | SAP

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

WELLS FARGO, Charlotte, SC.

2021 - 2023

# **Information Security Engineering Analyst**

Monitored and maintained six data centers using IBM Guardium covering 15,000 appliances. Searched, troubleshot, restarted, analyzed, and removed inactive and problematic appliances, using daily reports, data dashboards from Splunk and Guardium in order for operation stability.

- Collaborated with different teams from different timezones, with Scrum and Agile mindset, in order to find and fix problems. Participated in migrations to new software and decommissioning old ones.
- Installed new patches, updated software version to maintain cybersecurity level. Continuous learning on cloud structures and updated skillsets.

## **DOLLAR TREE DISTRIBUTION CENTER, Cowpens, SC.**

2019 - 2020

# **System Integration Technician**

Optimized, troubleshot, and repaired automation and robotic systems (AS/RS) using diagnostics tools and problem-solving skills. Find tools, software or schematics in order to do so. Sometimes, made it myself.

- Pointed engineers to where and how problems came to exist and also provided solutions on how to remove them. This helps them extensively in programming it.
- Writing detailed and concise reports with data analysis to management. Resulted with greatly increased output for the robotic work capacity and operation duration.

# MICHELIN NORTH AMERICA, Spartanburg, SC

2017 - 2019

#### **Tech Scholar**

Assisted in preventive maintenance and other associated tasks including quality audits, documentations and writing work instructions. Often, participating in brainstorming sessions on improving the skills of our team, the effectiveness of our methods.

- Trained newcomers and old-school mechanics on how a particular system works.
- Due to work ethics and the support of the team, managed to save the company 250,000 USD, in shutting down an air compressor for the pneumatic systems along with other achievements.

CONTEC INC. 2016 – 2017

**Laundry Operator** 

Assisted engineers, maintenance and managers in troubleshooting and optimizing the work process, with my prepared written and mental notes (filled with data and dates).

- Unofficially the leader of the work cell, planned the process, set the pacing and acted as the material carrier while loading over 2000lbs of material to laundry machines daily.
- By these actions, the production quota was able to expand by 50%.

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Machine-Learning for Films and Streaming Sites**

https://github.com/Hong-webport/Guessing-Projector-Clone-/tree/main/Final-Project-main/Final-Project-main | https://public.tableau.com/profile/hong.data.learn#!/vizhome/FinalProject11-19-20155Should-be-the-Finale/TheJourney

- The group objective is to use machine learning for several datasets obtained and applied machinelearning to predict which sites new movies may show up in. Created algorithms to extract information from multiple sources for several hundred of thousands of movies.
- Tools / languages used: Python (Pandas, Json, SKlearns, Numpy), Github, Tableau.

## **ETL Project**

https://github.com/Hong-webport/PokeETL | https://hong-webport.github.io/poke-tree/abb-index.html

- The group's objective is to extract and transform datas from an API into a website that acts as archives/navigation tools for enthusiasts for Pokemon series. live-search functions.
- Tools / languages used: Javascript (D3, Bootstrap4), Github.

# **Weather Data Visualizations Project**

https://github.com/Hong-webport/Weather-SnapShot | https://hong-webport.github.io/Web-Design-Challenge/landing.html

- Created a site to navigate and view weather data for cities around the globe.
- Tools / languages used: Python (Pandas, JSON, Matplotlib), Javascript (Bootstrap4).

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bootcamp Certificate**

Georgia Tech Professional Education

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Python, R, JavaScript, SQL Databases, Tableau, Big Data, and Machine Learning, Excel, VBA.

# Associate of Applied Science, AAS, in Mechatronics

Spartanburg Community College.

A 2-year work-study program focused on gaining technical troubleshooting skills and maintaining robotics and automations along with understanding of industrial process controls.

#### **Bachelor of Professional Design**

Limkokwing University of Creative Technology.

A 4-year program in the creative industry, with great focus on creating customer-centric design, marketing campaigns and creative problem-solvings based on comprehensive research, visual communication and technical skills.

## Other CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Azure AZ-900 | Splunk Foundamentals II | Kuka Robots Kore Certification